<topics>
<topic>
<number>1</number>
<title>
What is the difference between sex and love?
</title>
<description>
A potentially younger user has heard people talk about "good sex" only being possible in a loving relationship. They now want to know what people look for when just being interested in sex or, in contrast, what characterizes a loving relationship.   
</description>
<narrative>
Relevant documents will contain some description or explanation of what sex and/or love is. A highly relevant document will even contrast sex-only from loving relationships with some potential background of what people are looking for in either direction.
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>2</number>
<title>
Which is better, a laptop or a desktop?
</title>
<description>
A user wants to buy a new PC but has no prior preferences. They want to find arguments that show in what personal situation what kind of machine is preferable. This can range from situations like frequent traveling where a mobile device is to be favored to situations of a rather "stationary" gaming desktop PC.  
</description>
<narrative>
Highly relevant documents will describe the major similarities and dissimilarities of laptops and desktops along with the respective advantages and disadvantages of specific usage scenarios. A comparison of the technical and architectural characteristics without personal opinion, recommendation, or pros/cons is not relevant.
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>3</number>
<title>
Which is better, Canon or Nikon?
</title>
<description>
A user wants to buy a new camera from one of the two popular brands they have heard of. Since no further context is given, the user is interested in comparing Canon to Nikon cameras at different price/performance levels.
</description>
<narrative>
Highly relevant documents will compare pairs of cameras from the two popular camera manufacturers in different price/performance ranges (from entry-level models to professional equipment)---even optional potential suggestions of favorable cameras from other manufacturers may be contained. A document is relevant if at least some pair of Canon and Nikon cameras are compared or information about either of the cameras is provided but not just on the "technical" specs level. Documents without personal opinion, recommendation, and pros/cons are not relevant. 
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>4</number>
<title>
What are the best dish detergents?
</title>
<description>
A user is unsure about their currently used dish detergent and is looking for potential alternatives. A collection of what detergent is favored by others in what situations (e.g., allergies, environmentalism) would support a potential educated choice or a change of the used detergent.
</description>
<narrative>
Highly relevant documents will include a list with different types/brands of dish detergents and must include "recommendations" for one or different situations. Relevant documents may only contain suggestions not comparing different options. Both, expert reviews and personal opinions, are relevant but for instance plain lists of ingredients are not.       
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>5</number>
<title>
What are the best cities to live in?
</title>
<description>
Every now and then some list with the greenest / bike-friendliest / comfortable to live / etc. cities in the world is published. The user is looking for such lists of world-wide comparisons but with an explanation for the ranking like arguments for why one city is considered greener or more bike-friendly than another.
</description>
<narrative>
Both, opinions on a single city or ranked lists of cities based on the "objective" ratings or opinions are relevant when the documents include explanations of what criteria they consider important to explain green / bike-friendly / comfortable to live / etc. A highly relevant document will combine different notions of "best" in the ranking along with explanations for the ranking. Documents covering countries instead of cities or only cities from some smaller region are not relevant.
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>6</number>
<title>
What is the longest river in the U.S.?
</title>
<description>
During a pub quiz, a participating group needs to name the longest river in the U.S. To be more confident about the final answer, a list of the longest rivers and their length, as well as the criteria to measure length, may be helpful (e.g., length by the longest stem or total length of the whole river system).
</description>
<narrative>
Highly relevant documents will contain the names and lengths of different long U.S. rivers---ideally ordered by length---along with a criterion for measuring the length. A relevant document contains at least the name of the longest river and the information that it is the longest river in the U.S. along with a piece of information about the length measurement (e.g., longest stem: Missouri River, 3,768km according to Wikipedia [https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_longest_rivers_of_the_United_States_(by_main_stem)]; longest river system: Mississippi-Missouri-Jefferson-Beaverhead-Red Rock-Hell Roaring, 6,275km according to Wikipedia [https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/List_of_rivers_by_length], etc.).
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>7</number>
<title>
Which is healthiest: coffee, green tea or black tea and why?
</title>
<description>
A big coffee lover pursuing a healthy lifestyle has heard different opinions on the health benefits and harms of various hot drinks. Now they want to collect more opinions and expert knowledge on the issue to include one or another hot drink or exclude them from their diet.
</description>
<narrative>
Relevant documents containing facts and opinions may describe health benefits and potential harms of the three hot drinks mentioned in the question. Highly relevant documents must include clear expert knowledge supported by experimental data. A conclusion of which product is the healthiest or most harmful should be explicitly stated.          
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>8</number>
<title>
What are the advantages and disadvantages of PHP over Python and vice versa?
</title>
<description>
With no previous coding experience, a young user plans to start learning programming mostly for web development by attending a course at a coding school. But they have seen some online comments on the advantages and disadvantages of these two programming languages. Given a limited amount of time (and money), the user wants to choose just one course to learn coding in either language and needs to be sure to choose the better option.     
</description>
<narrative>
Relevant documents may contain an overview of more than these two programming languages and can include subjective opinions of anonymous online users and experienced coders. Highly relevant documents should include an explicit and justified recommendation on which of the languages to better start within what scenarios (e.g., job perspectives or ease of including deep learning pipelines). 
</narrative>
</topic>

<topic>
<number>9</number>
<title>
Why is Linux better than Windows?
</title>
<description>
Being tired of uncontrolled updates, a Windows user is thinking about switching to another operating system, for example, Linux strongly suggested as "better" by a geek friend. The Windows user knows this would cost them some time and effort to get familiar with Linux and decides to search online for more evidence about Linux advantages.
</description>
<narrative>
Given a specific intent to find information in support of the decision to switch to Linux, highly relevant documents should explicitly mention the advantages of Linux over Windows and/or disadvantages of Windows. Relevant documents can be limited to more general overviews of different operating systems including Linux and Windows and maybe not focused on the superiority of Linux only.    
</narrative>
</topic>
</topics>
